Finding Aid for A. Alfred Taubman College of Architecture + Urban Planning Records 1876-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Topical Files 1926-2004
  - 1967-2004
    - General Files 1967-2000
      - Exhibits
        - General 1976, 1980-1982 (Box 70)
      - Faculty Development Fund 1977-1987, 3 folders (Box 70)
      - Frank Lloyd Wright 1989-1990 (Box 70)
      - Press Releases: Lectures, Exhibits, and Other Events 1996-1998 (Box 70)
      - Student Report: "Saint Mary's Catholic Church, Manchester, MI," by John Joseph Linn for Architecture 503, Professor Eaton, Winter 1983 (Box 70)
      - Svoboda, Joseph 1980-1983 (Box 70)
        (scattered, part of Cross Currents Festival program)
      - Taubman Articles 1999-2003, 4 folders (Box 70)
      - Taubman Letters 1999-2003 (Box 70)
      - Unistrut Corporation 1991 (Box 71)
      - University Faculty Awards 1967-1986 (scattered), 2 folders (Box 71)
      - "Update" -- internal faculty and staff newsletter May 1986 (Box 71)
      - Urban and Regional Planning (URP) Faculty and Student Research 1998-1999 (Box 71)
      - Urban and Regional Planning Program -- Vision 2010 Student Input, May-June 1996 (folded large poster) (Box 71)
      - Willeke Design Competition 1983-1991
        - 1983
          - General (Box 71)
          - Photographs (Box 71)
        - 1984
          - General (Box 71)
          - Photographs (Box 71)
        - 1985 (Box 71)
        - 1986 (Box 71)
        - 1988 (Box 71)
        - 1989 (Box 71)
        - 1991 (Box 71)
        - Correspondence 1982-1987 (Box 71)
    - Lectures 1979-2004
      - Correspondence with Visiting Lecturers
        - 1979-1988, 10 folders (Box 71)
        - 1998-1999 (Box 71)
      - Dinkeloo Memorial Lecture (John Dinkeloo) (Box 72)
        - 1983-1993, 7 folders (Box 72)
        - 1995-1996 (Box 72)
      - Eames Memorial Program (a.k.a. Eames Memorial Lecture) 1982-1987 (scattered) (Box 72)
      - Posters 1988-2002 (Box 72)
      - Series Schedules
        - 1988-1993, 7 folders (Box 72)
        - 1999-2001, 3 folders (Box 72)
        - 2003-2004 (Box 72)
- Administrative Files 1926-2008
  The Administrative Files series (12 linear ft.) is comprised of the following subseries: William Werner, Development, and Personnel, Program Chair, and Associate Deans.
  - Werner, William
    Professor William Werner, recipient of numerous professional awards, including more than one for teaching excellence, also served as Chairperson, Bachelor of Science Program from 1977 to 1983 and Assistant to the Architecture Program Chairperson from 1983 to 1992. Since Werner was primarily concerned with admissions, counseling and curriculum while fulfilling these roles, the files are a good source for information on the day-to-day administrative workings of the college. The records offer a window into nearly twenty years of the evolution of the architectural program at Michigan through syllabi, surveys, planning and orientation, and similar documents.
    - Academic Requirements 1978 (Box 35)
    - Admissions Reports 1986-1995 (Box 35)
    - Admission Statistics 1973-1981 (Box 35)
    - Affirmative Action 1981-1998 (Box 35)
    - Assistants, Student 1979-1988 (Box 35)
    - Calendars 1992-1997 (Box 35)
    - Complaints 1978-1997 (Box 22)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2027 ]
    - Construction 1980-1985 (Box 35)
    - Counseling 1972-1977 (Box 35)
    - Course Review 1998 (Box 35)
    - Curriculum Issues 1976-1995, 2 folders (Box 35)
    - Dean Search 1992-1994 (Box 22)
    - Deanship 1985-1996 (Box 22)
    - Design 1976-1980 (Box 35)
    - Design Fund 1985-1986
    - Energy / Technology 1976-1977 (Box 35)
    - Endowment Income 1981-1982 (Box 35)
    - English Proficiency 1983-1985 (Box 35)
    - Evaluations, Course 1986-1991 (Box 35)
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes 1992-1995 (Box 35)
    - Faculty Retreat 1980 (Box 35)
    - History 1977-1978 (Box 35)
    - Marygrove 1998 (Box 35)
    - Metcalf Reports 1976-1981 (Box 35)
    - Miscellaneous 1984-1987 (Box 35)
    - National Architectural Accrediting Board (NAAB) 1976-1989 (Box 35)
    - Objectives / Mission 1975-1985 (Box 35)
    - Orientation 1979-1996 (Box 35)
    - Orientation, Year 3 1982-1995 (Box 36)
    - Personnel 1972-1992 (Box 22)
    - Planning 1982-1985 (Box 36)
    - Program Chair 1996-1997 (Box 36)
    - Promotions / Appointments 1976-1997, 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Research 1979-1993 (Box 36)
    - ROTC 1978-1984 (Box 36)
    - Rules 1972-1986 (Box 36)
    - School of Natural Resources 1973-1980 (Box 36)
    - Students in Governance 1976-1983 (Box 36)
    - Survey, Alum 1981 (Box 36)
    - Survey, B.S. 1981 (Box 36)
    - Syllabi 1976-1995, 3 folders (Box 36)
    - Teaching Assignments 1975-1994 (Box 36)
    - Visual Education 1977 (Box 36)
  - Development
    The Development subseries includes resources on funds and fellowships, significant alumni, and fund raising projects. The subseries is organized in two alphabetical files, reflecting multiple accessions. A 1996 promotional CD-Rom created by Lee Liming highlights the college in an on-line tour of North Campus, presents staff in classroom settings, profiles students, and focuses on research current at the time. The Development subseries also includes a number of folders relating to the A. Alfred Taubman endowment that led to the school adopting its current name. While most of the material documents the event celebrating the receipt of the gift and the renaming, files also include strategic planning documents and the proposal created for Mr. Taubman outlining proposed uses for the endowment.
    - 1974-1996
      - Alumni Steering Committee 1983-1987 (Box 36)
      - Alumni Records 1972-1973 (Box 36)
      - Development Committee 1982-1984 (Box 36)
      - Endowment Funds 1986 (Box 36)
      - Files, Individuals
        - Black, Kenneth 1974-1991 (Box 36)
        - Colvin, Huston 1979-1995 (Box 36)
        - Gabler, Cornelius 1988 (Box 36)
        - Gerganoff, Mary Louise 1988-1997 (Box 36)
        - Kideney, James William 1992-1994 (Box 36)
        - Kahmann, Bernice 1989-1990 (Box 36)
        - Miller, Vincent 1993-1999 (Box 36)
        - Moore, Charles 1987-1994, 2 folders (Box 36)
          (includes material relating to honorary degree and 2 photographs)
        - Schafer, Gilbert 1986-1996, 2 folders (Box 36)
        - Young, Griffith 1986-1988 (Box 36)
      - Funds and Fellowships (Box 37)
        - Frances and Gilbert Schafer Visiting Professional Fund 1986-1987 (Box 37)
        - J. Robert F. Swanson Estate 1981-1988 (Box 37)
        - Levine Fund 1985-1987 (Box 37)
        - Martin Luther King Memorial Fund 1990-1991 (Box 37)
        - Miscellaneous Endowments 1977-1985 (Box 37)
        - Sanders Memorial Fund 1983 (Box 37)
        - Seabury, Charles Ward, Fellowship 1986 (Box 37)
        - Taubman Chair 1978 (Box 37)
      - Fund Raising Prospects 1982-1987 (Box 37)
      - Graduation Lists 1909-1968 (Box 37)
      - Phonathon 1985 (Box 37)
      - President's Club 1975-1984 (Box 37)
      - Promotional CD-Rom 1996, 1 optical disks CD-ROMs (Box 37)
        (Includes welcoming statements, research, mission, student profiles, history, tour)
        (System requirements: Macintosh 68030 processor or higher, 6MB RAM, 10MB hard disk space, Quicktime 2.0)
    - 1987-2001
      - Arts Foundation of Michigan 1988-1989 (Box 54)
      - Bailey, Elizabeth Lorch 1987-1994 (Box 54)
      - Boone, Daniel 1990-1996 (Box 54)
      - Brown, H. Sanborn 1994-1997 (Box 54)
      - Cummins Engine Foundation 1988 (Box 54)
      - Danielson, Ralph 1991-2000 (Box 54)
      - Denler, William 1993 (Box 54)
      - Giffels Associates 1981-1988 (Box 54)
      - Goo, Donald 1990-1993 (Box 54)
      - Harris, Clark 1988-1993 (Box 54)
      - Haworth Furniture 1988 (Box 54)
      - Homer Hoyt Institute 1988-1996 (Box 54)
      - Martec Plastics 1988 (Box 54)
      - Muschenheim, William 1988-1993 (Box 54)
      - Taubman, Alfred 1999-2001, 4 folders (Box 54)
  - Personnel 1909-1989
    The Personnel subseries includes promotion reviews, arranged chronologically from 1986 to 1994 and past faculty files, arranged alphabetically, along with several general personnel files. Past faculty records date from 1909 to 1989, although researchers should note that file folder dates do not necessarily represent the time period served. The folders sometimes include correspondence or clippings received or filed after a faculty member left the college. Content ranges widely, from a single page for a one-semester visiting professor, to a significant collection of documents for some long time staff. In the case of the latter, there is often correspondence, a photograph, vitae, sabbatical reports, and similar items.
    - Faculty Activities and Evaluations 1980-1988, 8 folders (Box 38)
    - Promotions and Merit Increases
      - Prior to 1967 (Box 38)
      - 1967-1976, 8 folders (Box 38)
      - 1976-1986, 7 folders (Box 38)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2016 ]
    - Promotion Reviews
      - 1986
        - George Vakalo, 2 folders (Box 38)
      - 1988 (Box 39)
        - Hemalata Dandekar (Box 39)
        - Mitchell Rycus, 3 folders (Box 39)
      - 1989
        - Margaret Dewar, 2 folders (Box 39)
        - George Vakalo (Box 39)
      - 1990 (Box 40)
        - Robert Johnson, 2 folders (Box 40)
          [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2020 ]
      - 1991
        - James A. Turner, 2 folders (Box 40)
          [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2021 ]
      - 1992
        - Dean Almy (Interim) (Box 40)
      - 1993 [
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2023] ]
        - Thomas Hille, 4 folders (Box 40)
      - 1994
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2024] ]
        - Bradford Angelini (Box 40)
        - William Bricken (Interim) (Box 40)
        - Jong-Jin Kim (Interim) (Box 40)
        - Kent Kleinman (Interim) (Box 41)
        - Jonathan Levine (Interim) (Box 41)
        - Sharon Sutton, 5 folders (Box 41)
      - 1995
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2025 ]
        - Linda Groat (Box 41)
    - Past Faculty
      - Abdou, Ossama 1982 (Box 41)
      - Adiv, Aaron 1978-1987 (Box 41)
      - Akerman, Joseph 1967-1980 (Box 41)
      - Albano, Joseph 1947-1970 (Box 41)
      - Aldrich, Fred 1926-1943 (Box 41)
      - Allan, Maurice 1974-1976 (Box 41)
      - Allan, Harry 1947-1948 (Box 41)
      - Andringa, Gordon 1968-1969 (Box 42)
      - Arola, Frank 1986-1987 (Box 42)
      - Ash, Percy 1909-1926 (Box 42)
      - Bailey, Roger 1932-1948 (Box 42)
      - Barth, William 1968-1974 (Box 42)
      - Barnum, C.R. 1926-1933 (Box 42)
      - Bassett, Gregory 1948-1955 (Box 42)
      - Bauer, Dian 1977 (Box 42)
      - Bechhoefer, Arthur 1974-1975 (Box 42)
      - Belser, Karl 1941-1942 (Box 42)
      - Benson, Robert 1984-1985 (Box 41)
      - Berla, Michael 1977-1979 (Box 41)
      - Bergsma, Donald 1956-1957 (Box 41)
      - Bergum, Kathleen 1982 (Box 41)
      - Bernstein, Robert 1942 (Box 41)
      - Bess, Philip 1988-1989 (Box 41)
      - Black, Richard 1970-1976 (Box 41)
      - Blackie, Norman 1979-1983 (Box 41)
      - Blair, Robert 1969-1970 (Box 42)
      - Blum, Sigmund 1972-1973 (Box 42)
      - Borton, Thomas 1971-1974 (Box 42)
      - Boyton, Louis 1912-1924 (Box 42)
      - Brady, Rufus 1950 (Box 42)
      - Brosa, Victor 1986-1987 (Box 42)
      - Brownson, Jacques 1965-1968 (Box 42)
      - Buck, James 1963-1964 (Box 42)
      - Bunting, William 1967-1974 (Box 42)
      - Carlson, William 1937 (Box 42)
      - Carpenter, Robert 1964-1968 (Box 42)
      - Carson, Daniel 1967 (Box 42)
      - Cedercreutz, Mariana 1974-1975 (Box 42)
      - Chamberlain, Samuel 1925-1926 (Box 42)
      - Christensian, Keith 1955 (Box 42)
      - Clampitt, Ralph 1969-1971 (Box 42)
      - Clausen, Leslie 1946 (Box 42)
      - Clemence, Roger 1962-1965 (Box 42)
      - Contreras, Carlos 1941 (Box 42)
      - Costello, James 1964-1976 (Box 42)
      - Coy, Paul Henry 1946-1957 (Box 42)
      - Crane, Maria 1926-1931 (Box 42)
      - Crowell, Elizabeth 1976-1978 (Box 42)
      - Dawson, John 1956-1963 (Box 42)
      - Dewinter, Marvin 1959 (Box 42)
      - Della Salla, Francesco 1949-1957 (Box 42)
      - Dietz, Albert 1976-1977 (Box 42)
      - Ditchy, Clair 1930-1956 (Box 42)
      - Eastman, Raye 1948-1949 (Box 42)
      - Ehler, Charles 1966-1968 (Box 43)
      - Elgaaly, Mohamed 1979-1986 (Box 43)
      - Enersen, Lawrence 1940-1958 (Box 43)
      - Erikson, Bruce 1960-1969 (Box 43)
      - Erskine, Robert 1968-1980 (Box 43)
      - Falkson, Joseph 1970 (Box 43)
      - Fanelli, Franco 1957-1958 (Box 43)
      - Farber, Erich 1974-1975 (Box 43)
      - Gamble, Henry 1927-1930 (Box 43)
      - Friedman, Yona 1967-1972 (Box 43)
      - Fowler, Herbert 1923-1938 (Box 43)
      - Flynn, John 1965-1980 (Box 43)
      - Fisher, Emil 1950-1952 (Box 43)
      - Ganapathy, R. S. 1979-1980 (Box 43)
      - Gardner, William 1973-1981 (Box 43)
      - Gazzarato, Rosemarie 1988-1989 (Box 43)
      - Gehner, Martin 1960-1970 (Box 43)
      - Greenhalph, Donald 1959-1960 (Box 43)
      - Griffith, John 1953-1954 (Box 43)
      - Grossjean, Robert 1956-1957 (Box 43)
      - Growald, Martin 1957-1958 (Box 43)
      - Guenther, Karl 1974-1978 (Box 43)
      - Gustavs, Erland 1982-1984 (Box 43)
      - Hacin, Janez 1961-1962 (Box 43)
      - Haecker, James 1962-1963 (Box 43)
      - Haga, Thomas 1970-1974 (Box 43)
      - Hammarskjold, Edward 1953-1962 (Box 43)
      - Hampikian, Hrand 1942 (Box 43)
      - Hayward, William 1957-1958 (Box 43)
      - Herbard, Jean 1931-1959 (Box 43)
      - Hopkins, Eugene 1987 (Box 43)
      - Howe, Austin 1926-1936 (Box 43)
      - Hyde, John 1945-1985 (Box 43)
      - Jackson, William 1982 (Box 43)
      - Jaroszewicz, Mark 1969-1970 (Box 43)
      - Jemadari, Kawara Swan 1984-1985 (Box 43)
      - Jenks, Barton 1940 (Box 43)
      - Juarez, Fernando 1958 (Box 43)
      - Kartadiwiria, Z. 1962 (Box 43)
      - Kelly, Burnham 1956 (Box 43)
      - Kersten, Lawrence 1969-1971 (Box 43)
      - Knott, Albert 1962 (Box 43)
      - Kronick, T. Gerald 1930-1932 (Box 43)
      - Ku, Anna 1979-1980 (Box 43)
      - LeFeure, Michael 1981 (Box 43)
      - Legrand, Roger 1949-1951 (Box 43)
      - LeRicolais, Robert 1956-1960 (Box 43)
      - Lerski, Hanna 1974 (Box 43)
      - London, Edmund 1962-1963 (Box 43)
      - Long, Stephen 1949 (Box 43)
      - Loomis, Charles 1920-1922 (Box 43)
      - Makielski, Leon 1918-1923 (Box 43)
      - Manian, Venkat 1988-1989 (Box 43)
      - Mano, Kiyoshi 1956-1983 (Box 43)
      - Marshall, Walter 1925-1967 (Box 43)
      - Mathews, Raymond 1931-1935 (Box 43)
      - Mautz, Robert 1972-1975 (Box 43)
      - Merrill, John 1972-1976 (Box 43)
      - Miller, Pat 1975-1980 (Box 43)
      - Milliken, John Douglas 1963-1964 (Box 43)
      - Monroe, Susan 1983 (Box 43)
      - Montgomery, Daniel 1974-1975 (Box 43)
      - Morris, Harry 1948 (Box 43)
      - Muldenhauer, Judith 1989 (Box 43)
      - Mundt, Ernest 1940-1944 (Box 43)
      - Newman, Richard 1978-1981 (Box 43)
      - Newman, Christine 1921-1976 (Box 43)
      - Noble, Charles 1926 (Box 43)
      - Olencki, Edward (see box 7) (Box 43)
      - O'Dell, Frederick 1920-1979 (Box 43)
      - Pearman, Charles 1948-1959 (Box 43)
      - Pelikan, Alfred 1923 (Box 43)
      - Phillipides, Dimitri 1972-1984 (Box 43)
      - Poley, Lincoln 1986-1987 (Box 43)
      - Prak, Niels Luning 1972-1985 (Box 43)
      - Prussin, Labelle 1972-1977 (Box 43)
      - Rasid, Hani 1989 (Box 43)
      - Refuerzo, Ben 1979-1982 (Box 44)
      - Resnick, David 1991-1992 (Box 44)
      - Robinson, Sidney 1973-1981 (Box 44)
      - Rogers, Gordon 1961-1962 (Box 44)
      - Rolfsen, N. Gerald 1968-1978 (Box 44)
      - Ross, George 1939-1959 (Box 44)
      - Rosseau, Albert Joseph 1983-1986 (Box 44)
      - Sanders, Walter (see box 7) (Box 44)
      - Savin, Joseph 1959-1975 (Box 44)
      - Schmiedeke, Denis 1975 (Box 44)
      - Schmult, Carl 1965-1970 (Box 44)
      - Seidel, Peter 1965-1969 (Box 44)
      - Selland, O. Thomas 1977-1978 (Box 44)
      - Sherman, Stanley 1956-1961 (Box 44)
      - Shreve, Gerry 1976-1978 (Box 44)
      - Skinner, Donald 1964 (Box 44)
      - Skrubb, George 1971 (Box 44)
      - Slack, Robert 1939-1940 (Box 44)
      - Slocum, Victor Vaughn 1926-1931 (Box 44)
      - Sorise, Frank 1985-1986 (Box 44)
      - Stevens, Robert 1969-1971 (Box 44)
      - Stino, Laila 1973-1978 (Box 44)
      - Sullivan, Carol 1983-1985 (Box 44)
      - Takaichi, Robert 1959-1963 (Box 44)
      - Tanner, Thomas 1927-1964 (Box 44)
      - Taylor, Albert 1939-1942 (Box 44)
      - Taylor, Jonathan 1948 (Box 44)
      - Trout, Alexander 1925 (Box 44)
      - Tsuchiya, Harold 1974-1976 (Box 44)
      - Van Moltke, William 1952 (Box 44)
      - Van Osdol, Nathan 1949-1950 (Box 44)
      - Van Pelt, Robert 1986-1987 (Box 44)
      - Warren, Rachelle 1977-1978 (Box 44)
      - Weise, Frank 1948-1949 (Box 44)
      - Welch, Lyndon 1949-1980 (Box 44)
      - Weyland, Hendrick 1963 (Box 44)
      - White, Hubert 1967-1968 (Box 44)
      - Whittemore, Harlow 1941-1973 (Box 44)
      - Wilby, Ernest 1922-1956 (Box 44)
      - Williams, Michael 1989 (Box 44)
      - Wineman, Jean 1975-1977 (Box 44)
      - Wong, James 1984-1986 (Box 44)
      - Wood, Roscoe 1927-1930 (Box 44)
      - Woodworth, Lilburn 1946-1950 (Box 44)
      - Wotten, Earnest 1974-1975 (Box 44)
      - Young, Todd 1987-1989 (Box 44)
      - Youtz, Philip 1957-1975 (Box 44)
      - Zuck, Stanley Franklin 1934-1936 (Box 44)
  - Program Chair
    The Program Chair subseries is comprised of Brian Carter correspondence arranged alphabetically in two runs.
    - Brian Carter
      - 1994-1995 (Box 52)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 53)
  - Associate Deans
    Associate Dean files include the records of Linda Groat, topically arranged; several Robert Johnson folders, unarranged; and one James Snyder folder. The Groat records are primarily concerned with the college's participation in the various Michigan Mandate programs of the period initiated by President Duderstadt.
    - Linda Groat
      - Affirmative Action 1988-1992 (Box 53)
      - Black and White Styles 1989 (Box 53)
      - College Days 1989-1993 (Box 53)
      - Disabilities 1988 (Box 53)
      - Discrimination 1988 (Box 53)
      - Dual Career 1989 (Box 53)
      - King/Chavez/Parks Visiting Professor 1988-1994, 3 folders (Box 53)
      - Minorities in Architecture 1989 (Box 53)
      - Multicultural 1990-1992 (Box 53)
      - New Instructional Staff of Color 1991-1996 (Box 53)
      - Sexual Discrimination 1990 (Box 53)
      - Student Recruiting 1988 (Box 53)
      - Student Stats 1980-1989 (Box 53)
    - Robert Johnson 1992-1996
      - 1992-1993, 2 folders (Box 53)
      - 1994-1995, 3 folders (Box 54)
    - Snyder, James C. 1996 (Box 54)
  - Development 1987-2006
    The Development sub-series, 1987-2006 includes folders relating to alumni and fundraising events, and individual donors. The files also contain materials on the Capital Campaign, including Capital Campaign Advisory Committee (CAC) meetings.
    - Alumni Society Board of Governors 2003-2006 (Box 64)
    - Campaign Literature (UM) -- "The Michigan Difference," 2004 (Box 64)
    - Capital Campaign
      - Campaign Advisory Committee (CAC) Meetings
        - September 28, 2001 (Box 64)
        - February 8, 2002 (Box 64)
        - September 20, 2002 (Box 64)
        - February 6, 2003 (Box 64)
        - February 7, 2004 (Box 64)
      - Fund Drive -- Board 2000-2004 (Box 64)
    - Chicago Alumni Reception
      - December 1990 (Box 64)
      - April 1992 (Box 64)
    - Files, Individuals
      - Brademas, Tom (Box 64)
      - Bund, Sally and Ian (Box 64)
      - Gerson, Ralph (Box 64)
      - Glieberman, Bernie (Box 64)
      - Palmer, Mary (Box 64)
      - Polk, Sharon Madison (Box 64)
      - Silverman, Buzz (Box 64)
      - Strather, Herb (Box 64)
      - Suomi, Marvin (Box 64)
      - Teran, Jose and Maria (Box 64)
      - Van Sweden, James (Box 64)
      - Winkelman, Peggy and Stanley (photo included in the file) (Box 64)
    - Fundraising 2006 (Box 64)
    - Hockey Game (UM) January 2001 (Box 64)
    - Kresge Foundation (Elizabeth Sullivan) 2001-2002 (Box 64)
    - Longo Dinner Party (Alumni -- Chicago) July 2003 (Box 64)
    - Los Angeles Area Alumni Dinner March 1987 (Box 64)
    - New York City Alumni Reception January 2000 (Box 64)
    - San Francisco Luncheon November 1991 (Box 64)
    - Smith Hinchman and Grylls Alumni Reception September 1991 (Box 64)
    - STOREFRONT for Art and Architecture Reception June 1991 (Box 64)
    - Suomi's Dinner -- Los Angeles May 2002 (Box 64)
    - Washtenaw County Alumni Reception April 1987 (Box 64)
  - Personnel 1998-2008
    The Personnel, 1998-2008 subseries is divided into General Files, and Faculty and Staff Files. The General Files, 1997-2008 include college statistics, comparisons with other schools and colleges of architecture and urban planning, and salary charts. The Faculty and Staff Files, 1998-2008 are arranged alphabetically by faculty surnames and include correspondence, reports, and promotion and tenure reviews. Content within each folder varies, and researchers should note that the date range listed for the Faculty and Staff files is inclusive, but not all dates are represented in the individual files.
    - General Files
      - College Statistics 2004-2008 (Box 65)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2038 ]
      - Comparisons with Other Schools 1998-2006 (Box 65)
      - Personnel -- General 1997-2006 (Box 65)
      - Salary Charts 2000-2008 (Box 65)
    - Faculty and Staff Files 1998-2008
      - Adams, Robert (Box 65)
      - Allen, Peter (Box 65)
      - Arbogast-Wilson, Ken (Box 65)
      - Borum, Craig (Box 65)
      - Brownwell, Blaine (Box 65)
      - Buresh, Tom (Box 65)
      - Campbell, Scott (Box 65)
      - Chaffers, Jim (Box 65)
      - Checkoway, Barry (Box 65)
      - Correa, Nondita (Box 65)
      - Constant, Caroline (Box 65)
      - Daubmann, Karl (Box 65)
      - Deng, Lan (Box 65)
      - Dewar, Margaret (Margi) (Box 65)
      - Dimendberg, Ed (Box 65)
      - Drew, Mary Anne (Box 65)
      - Erickson, Donna (Box 65)
      - Fishman, Robert (Box 65)
      - Giles, Harry (Box 65)
      - Glover, Will (Box 65)
      - Grengs, Joe (Box 65)
      - Groat, Linda (Box 65)
      - Harris, Melissa (Box 65)
      - Harvey, Janice (Box 65)
      - Herscher, Andrew (Box 65)
      - Hill, Eric (Box 65)
      - Jackson, Shaun (Box 65)
      - Jordan, Coleman (Box 65)
      - Kennedy, Mick (Box 65)
      - Kim, Jong-Jin (J.J.) (Box 65)
      - Krecic, Mark (Box 65)
      - Kulper, Amy (Box 65)
      - Kulper, Perry (Box 65)
      - Lara, Fernando (Box 65)
      - Leinberger, Christopher (Box 65)
      - Levine, Jonathan (Box 65)
      - Manspeaker, Bill (Box 65)
      - McCullough, Kit (Box 65)
      - McCullough, Malcolm (Box 65)
      - Mills, Linda (Box 65)
      - Mitnick, Keith (Box 65)
      - Navvab, Mojtaba (Moji) (Box 65)
      - Norton, Richard (Box 65)
      - Osler, Peter (Box 65)
      - Pachikara, Cynthia (Box 65)
      - Psarra, Sophia (Box 65)
      - Ray, Mary-Anne (Box 65)
      - Roddier, Mireille (Box 65)
      - Rossin, Keria (Box 65)
      - Senkevitch, Anatole (Box 65)
      - Shatkin, Gavin (Box 65)
      - Soo, Lydia (Box 65)
      - Strickland, Roy (Box 65)
      - Taylor, Don (Box 65)
      - Thacher, David (Box 65)
      - Thomas, June Manning (Box 65)
      - Thun Geoffrey and Velikov, Kathy (Box 65)
      - Turner, Jim (Box 65)
      - Von Buelow, Peter (Box 65)
      - Walter, Beverly (Box 65)
      - Wilkins, Craig (Box 65)
      - Wilkins, Gretchen (Box 65)
      - Wineman, Jean (Box 65)
      - Young, Jason (Box 65)
      - Zimmerman, Claire (Box 65)
- Architectural Drawings